<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
   <rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
   <title>Brady Stroud Blog</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev</link>
   <description>Latest posts from Brady Stroud</description>
   
   <item>
   <title>Make Large-Scale Refactors Easy with Parallel AI Agents</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/easy-ai-refactors</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/easy-ai-refactors</guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Learn how to turn week-long refactors into 20-minute tasks using 15 AI agents working in parallel. A practical guide to distributed AI orchestration for large-scale code changes.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>Word Doc to PDF: Evaluating Tools and Landing on PowerAutomate</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/word-doc-to-pdf</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/word-doc-to-pdf</guid>
   <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Automated Word to PDF conversion is harder than it looks. Learn from our trials with Foxit PDF and IronPDF, and why Microsoft Power Automate won for pixel-perfect fidelity.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>OpenAI Chat Model Cheat Sheet - Decoding the Chaos</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/openai-model-cheatsheet</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/openai-model-cheatsheet</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>OpenAI model names (o4, 4o, 4.1) are confusing. Quick reference guide to GPT-5, GPT-4.1, mini, nano, and legacy models with strengths, trade-offs, and best use cases.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>Fixing the &#39;PowerShell session not found&#39; issue in VS Code</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/vscode-powershell-session-fix</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/vscode-powershell-session-fix</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Fix the &#39;PowerShell session not found&#39; error in VS Code by manually setting the PowerShell executable path. Quick solution for macOS users with Homebrew installations.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>Connecting Windows VMs to Mac-Hosted APIs</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/connect-windows-vm-to-mac-apis</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/connect-windows-vm-to-mac-apis</guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Securely connect Windows VM apps to Mac-hosted APIs using SSH tunnels and dev certificates. Complete guide for Parallels development with .NET and IdentityServer.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>.NET Aspire in Windows VM using Docker on the Mac Host</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/aspire-windows-vm</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/aspire-windows-vm</guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Run .NET Aspire in a Windows VM while leveraging macOS Docker daemon via SSH context. Avoid nested virtualization and Docker duplication on Apple Silicon Macs.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>Cocona - Clean console apps in .NET</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/cocona-console-apps</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/cocona-console-apps</guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Build clean .NET CLI apps with Cocona framework. Automatic help pages, dependency injection, and command parsing make console applications simple and maintainable.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>.NET MAUI setup on macOS - build once, run everywhere</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/maui-setup-macos</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/maui-setup-macos</guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Complete .NET MAUI setup guide for macOS. Install workload, Xcode, and Android Studio to build cross-platform apps for iOS, Android, and Mac with one codebase.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>Your Data Is Power - Even Your Search History</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/your-data-is-power</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/your-data-is-power</guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Companies combine your data for insights. Learn how to take back control by tracking your own Safari browser history with a simple macOS script and SQLite queries.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>RAID - Rapid AI Development</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/raid</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/raid</guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Use AI to build features fast, then replace with optimized code later. RAID approach lets you ship quickly while managing technical debt strategically.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>🚦 Loading Guards in Blazor - Stop Writing Null-Checks Everywhere</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/loading-guards-in-blazor</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/loading-guards-in-blazor</guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Eliminate scattered null-checks in Blazor with loading guard components. Clean pattern for handling async data loading with skeletons and progressive UI rendering.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>The Right Mobile App Framework - Comprehensive Decision Tree</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/app-framework-decision-tree</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/app-framework-decision-tree</guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Choose the right mobile framework with this decision tree. Compare PWA, React Native, Flutter, .NET MAUI, and native development based on your team and requirements.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>Guide to professional Growth</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/professional-growth</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/professional-growth</guid>
   <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Transition from developer to management with 4 proven strategies. Be visible, understand company goals, be memorable, and do the job you want before you have it.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>Cultural Exchange - 2 Months with SSW France</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/cultural-exchange</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/cultural-exchange</guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Two months living and working in Strasbourg with SSW France. First solo travel experience across 5 European countries with valuable lessons in independence and adaptability.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>.NET MAUI Blazor template - Build your UI once</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/maui-blazor</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/maui-blazor</guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>Build cross-platform apps with one shared Blazor UI codebase. Run on Android, iOS, Windows, macOS, and web using .NET MAUI and Blazor hybrid architecture.</description>
   </item>
   <item>
   <title>.NET MAUI vs Flutter - Multi-platform frameworks showdown</title>
   <link>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/maui-vs-flutter</link>
   <guid>https://bradystroud.dev/blogs/maui-vs-flutter</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <description>A hands-on comparison of .NET MAUI and Flutter for cross-platform development. Compare native UI, markup languages, and developer experience to choose the right framework.</description>
   </item>
   </channel>
   </rss>